<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cookies>
	<header>
			Privacy Policy
	</header>
	<updatetime>
		Last updated: January 21, 2019
	</updatetime>
	<topbody>
		<div1>
			Nanjing Yibai Info Tech Co., Ltd ("us", "we", or "our") considers the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy describes in detail the types of personal information collected and recorded on the http://www.100tefl.com website (the "Service") and how it is used. By using the Service, you consent to our privacy policy and agree to the following terms.

		</div1>
		<div2>
			If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email. 

		</div2>
		
	</topbody>
	<whararecookies>
		<h>
			Log Files
		</h>
		<div1>
			Like many other Web sites, www.100tefl.com makes use of log files. These files merely log visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’ analytics. 
		</div1>
		<div2>
			The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

		</div2>
	</whararecookies>
	<howweuse>
		<h>Cookies and Web Beacons</h>
		<div1>
			www.100tefl.com uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the site visitor accesses or visits, and to personalize or customize our web page content based upon visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
		</div1>
		<div2>
			For more on the use of cookies on our Service, please refer to our 
			<link>Cookies Policy.</link> 
		</div2>
	</howweuse>

	<choice>
		<h>
			Online Privacy Policy Only

		</h>
		<div1>
			This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there. This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this websites. 
		</div1>
	</choice>
	<consent>
		<h>
			Consent
		</h>
		<div1>
			By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
		</div1>
	</consent>
	<moreinfo>
		<h>
			Update
		</h>
		<body>
			This Privacy Policy was last updated on: Monday, January 21st, 2019.
			Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
		</body>
		
		
	</moreinfo>
	







</cookies>


 



