<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cookies>
	<header>
			Terms of Use
	</header>
	<updatetime>
		Last updated: January 21, 2019
	</updatetime>
	<subheader>
		1. Terms
	</subheader>
	<div1>
		By accessing the website at http://www.100tefl.com (the “Site”), or any services provided by Nanjing Yibai Info Tech Co., Ltd ("us", "we", or "our”), you are agreeing to be bound by these Terms of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are at least 18 years and are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. 
	</div1>
	<div2>
		It is your responsibility to review these Terms of Use periodically, and if at any time you find these Terms of Use unacceptable to you, you must immediately cease using this Site (the “Service”). The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS, YOU ARE PROHIBITED FROM USING OR ACCESSING THIS SITE.
	</div2>
	<subheader2>
		2. Privacy Policy
	</subheader2>
	<div3>
		We consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important and permit you to control the treatment of your personal information. Our complete Privacy Policy statement can be accessed by clicking the Privacy Policy link at the bottom of the home page or by clicking here. The Privacy Policy is incorporated into this Agreement by this reference.

	</div3>
	<subheader3>
		3. Cookies Policy
	</subheader3>
	<div4>
		We use cookies on this Service to enable us to provide certain services to our users. For more on our Cookies Policy click here or access the Cookies Policy by clicking the Cookies Policy link at the bottom of the home page. The Cookies Policy is expressly incorporated into this Agreement by this reference. 
	</div4>
	<subheader4>
		4. Accuracy of information and materials
	</subheader4>
	<div5>
		This site contains information in the form of posts, articles and videos that are provided for your education. The information is general in nature and is not intended in any way to act as accurate, complete or current information. The materials appearing on 100tefl.com's website could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. 100tefl.com does not warrant that any of the materials on its website are accurate, complete or current. 100tefl.com may make changes to the information or materials contained on its website at any time without notice. However, 100tefl.com does not make any commitment to update the materials. 

	</div5>
	<subheader5>
		5. User content

	</subheader5>
	<div6>
		<subdiv1>
			You may post comments to articles on this Site. In doing so, you grant Nanjing Yibai Info Tech Co., Ltd a license to use the materials you post to the Site or Service. By posting, downloading, displaying, performing, transmitting, or otherwise distributing information or other content (“User Content”) to the Site or Service, you are granting it, its affiliates, officers, directors, employees, consultants, agents, and representatives a license to use User Content in connection with the operation of the Site, its affiliates, officers, directors, employees, consultants, agents, and representatives, including without limitation, a right to copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate, and reformat User Content. You will not be compensated for any User Content.
		</subdiv1>
		<subdiv2>
			You agree that such comments are not protected and that Nanjing Yibai Info Tech Co., Ltd or 100tefl.com may publish or otherwise disclose your name in connection with your User Content. By posting User Content on the Site or Service, you warrant and represent that you own the rights to the User Content or are otherwise authorised to post, distribute, display, perform, transmit, or otherwise distribute User Content.

		</subdiv2>
	</div6>
	<subheader6>
		6. Compliance with Intellectual Property Laws
	</subheader6>
	<div7>
		<subdiv1>
			When accessing the Site or Service, you agree to obey the law and to respect the intellectual property rights of others. Your use of the Site and Service is governed by laws regarding copyright ownership and use of intellectual property. You agree not to upload, download, display, perform, transmit, or otherwise distribute any information or content (collectively, “Content”) in violation of any third party’s copyrights, trademarks, or other intellectual property or proprietary rights.
		</subdiv1>
		<subdiv2>
			You agree to abide by laws regarding copyright ownership and use of intellectual property, and you shall be solely responsible for any violations of any relevant laws and for any infringements of third party rights caused by any Content you provide or transmit, or that is provided or transmitted using your User ID. The burden of proving that any Content does not violate any laws or third party rights rests solely with you.

		</subdiv2>
	</div7>
	<subheader7>
		7. Inappropriate content
	</subheader7>
	<div8>
		<ol>
			You shall not make the following types of Content available. You agree not to upload, download, display, perform, transmit, or otherwise distribute any Content that:-
		</ol>
		
		 <l1>is libellous, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, abusive, or threatening;</l1>
		 <l2>advocates or encourages conduct that could constitute a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any applicable local, state, national, or foreign law or regulation;</l2>
		 <l3>advertises or otherwise solicits funds or is a solicitation for goods or services. Firm reserves the right to terminate your receipt, transmission, or other distribution of any such material using the Service, and, if applicable, to delete any such material from its servers. </l3>
	</div8>
	<subheader8>
		8. Alleged violations
	</subheader8>
	<div9>
		<subdiv1>
			Firm reserves the right to terminate your use of the Service and/or the Site. To ensure that 100tefl.com provides a high quality experience for you and for other users of the Site and the Service, you agree that 100tefl.com or its representatives may access your account and records on a case-by-case basis to investigate complaints or allegations of abuse, infringement of third party rights, or other unauthorized uses of the Site or the Service.
		</subdiv1>
		<subdiv2>
			100tefl.com does not intend to disclose the existence or occurrence of such an investigation unless required by law, but100tefl.com reserves the right to terminate your account or your access to the Site immediately, with or without notice to you, and without liability to you, if 100tefl.com believes that you have violated any of the Terms of Use, furnished 100tefl.com with false or misleading information, or interfered with use of the Site or the Service by others.
		</subdiv2>
	</div9>
	<subheader9>
		9. Affiliated Sites
	</subheader9>
	<div10>
		Nanjing Yibai Info Tech Co., Ltd has no control over, and no liability for any third party websites or materials that may be linked with the Site or Service. Because neither Nanjing Yibai Info Tech Co., Ltd or 100tefl.com has control over the content and performance over these third party sites, We make no guarantees about the accuracy, currency, content, or quality of the information provided by such sites, and We assume no responsibility for unintended, objectionable, inaccurate, misleading, or unlawful content that may reside on those sites. You acknowledge and agree that We make no guarantees about, and assume no responsibility for, the accuracy, currency, content, or quality of this third party content, and that, unless expressly provided otherwise, these Terms of Use shall govern your use of any and all third party content.
	</div10>
	<subheader10>
		10. Limitations
	</subheader10>
	<div11>
		In no event shall 100tefl.com or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on 100tefl.com's website, even if 100tefl.com or a 100tefl.com authorised representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. 
	</div11>
	<subheader11>
		11. Warranties
	</subheader11>
	<div12>
		<subdiv1>
			The materials on 100tefl.com's website are provided on an 'as is' basis. 100tefl.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.

		</subdiv1>
		<subdiv2>
			Further, 100tefl.com does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

		</subdiv2>
	</div12>
	<subheader12>
		12. Prohibited Uses
	</subheader12>
	<div13>
		<subdiv1>
			We impose certain restrictions on your permissible use of the Site and the Service. You are prohibited from violating or attempting to violate any security features of the Site or Service, including, without limitation
		</subdiv1>
		<l1>accessing content or data not intended for you, or logging onto a server or account that you are not authorised to access; </l1>
		<l2>attempting to probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of the Service, the Site, or any associated system or network, or to breach security or authentication measures without proper authorisation; </l2>
		<l3>interfering or attempting to interfere with service to any user, host, or network, including, without limitation, by means of submitting a virus to the Site or Service, overloading, “flooding,” “spamming,” “mail bombing,” or “crashing;”</l3>
		<l4>using the Site or Service to send unsolicited e-mail, including, without limitation, promotions, or advertisements for products or services; </l4>
		<l5>forging any TCP/IP packet header or any part of the header information in any e-mail or in any posting using the Service; </l5>
		<l6>attempting to modify, reverse-engineer, decompile, disassemble, or otherwise reduce or attempt to reduce to a human-perceivable form any of the source code used by Firm in providing the Site or Service. Any violation of system or network security may subject you to civil and/or criminal liability.</l6>
	</div13>
	<subheader13>
		13. License
	</subheader13>
	<div14>
		Your use of the Site does not constitute a license to use any of the trademarks, service marks, or logos owned by Us or by any third party.
	</div14>
	<subheader14>
		14. Warranties 
	</subheader14>
	<div15>
		<subdiv1>
			The materials on 100tefl.com's website are provided on an 'as is' basis. 100tefl.com makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.

		</subdiv1>
		<subdiv2>
			Further, 100tefl.com does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its website or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
		</subdiv2>
	</div15>
	<subheader15>
		15. Modifications
	</subheader15>
	<div16>
		100tefl.com may revise the Site and/or Service and the Terms of Use for its website at any time without notice. By using this website, you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of the Site, and Terms of Use.

	</div16>
	<subheader16>
		16. Governing Law

	</subheader16>
	<div17>
		These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Nanjing, China and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Nanjing, China in all disputes arising out of or related to the use of the Site or Service.
	</div17>
	<subheader17>
		17. Acknowledgement 	
	</subheader17>
	<div18>
		BY USING THE SERVICE OR ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ THESE TERMS OF USE AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THEM.
	</div18>
		






</cookies>


 



